[
  {
    "question": "10 x 17 =",
    "correct": 170,
    "choices": [
      121,
      170,
      -333,
      72
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 14 =",
    "correct": 238,
    "choices": [
      -178,
      -394,
      238,
      -292
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 18 =",
    "correct": 360,
    "choices": [
      -112,
      166,
      360,
      36
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 16 =",
    "correct": 304,
    "choices": [
      -377,
      244,
      304,
      -279
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 x 16 =",
    "correct": 288,
    "choices": [
      21,
      97,
      -35,
      288
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 18 =",
    "correct": 342,
    "choices": [
      -52,
      20,
      342,
      -115
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 x 14 =",
    "correct": 252,
    "choices": [
      252,
      -181,
      282,
      69
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 14 =",
    "correct": 280,
    "choices": [
      -114,
      280,
      -290,
      400
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 x 15 =",
    "correct": 195,
    "choices": [
      -220,
      1,
      195,
      119
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 15 =",
    "correct": 150,
    "choices": [
      150,
      -389,
      240,
      -92
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 11 =",
    "correct": 154,
    "choices": [
      154,
      68,
      -163,
      205
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11 x 14 =",
    "correct": 154,
    "choices": [
      154,
      -385,
      -351,
      363
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 11 =",
    "correct": 209,
    "choices": [
      255,
      -43,
      316,
      209
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 11 =",
    "correct": 209,
    "choices": [
      191,
      278,
      209,
      -6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 19 =",
    "correct": 190,
    "choices": [
      -207,
      190,
      -72,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 18 =",
    "correct": 252,
    "choices": [
      -130,
      102,
      365,
      252
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 12 =",
    "correct": 168,
    "choices": [
      -266,
      92,
      -57,
      168
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 19 =",
    "correct": 228,
    "choices": [
      228,
      -279,
      394,
      -95
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 15 =",
    "correct": 240,
    "choices": [
      109,
      240,
      136,
      -225
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 20 =",
    "correct": 200,
    "choices": [
      108,
      96,
      200,
      -199
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 x 10 =",
    "correct": 180,
    "choices": [
      15,
      -35,
      357,
      180
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 16 =",
    "correct": 160,
    "choices": [
      85,
      174,
      -138,
      160
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 14 =",
    "correct": 210,
    "choices": [
      -37,
      210,
      -192,
      30
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 16 =",
    "correct": 256,
    "choices": [
      -95,
      256,
      330,
      -372
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 15 =",
    "correct": 225,
    "choices": [
      -187,
      225,
      -362,
      -193
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 12 =",
    "correct": 192,
    "choices": [
      -261,
      192,
      -309,
      -283
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 11 =",
    "correct": 132,
    "choices": [
      280,
      132,
      -185,
      -48
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11 x 10 =",
    "correct": 110,
    "choices": [
      312,
      84,
      -104,
      110
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 16 =",
    "correct": 256,
    "choices": [
      256,
      -323,
      140,
      -247
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 16 =",
    "correct": 160,
    "choices": [
      -327,
      160,
      -377,
      186
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 13 =",
    "correct": 182,
    "choices": [
      320,
      -92,
      182,
      -219
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 17 =",
    "correct": 289,
    "choices": [
      379,
      137,
      -311,
      289
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 14 =",
    "correct": 196,
    "choices": [
      137,
      196,
      389,
      58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 16 =",
    "correct": 224,
    "choices": [
      -230,
      224,
      83,
      5
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 14 =",
    "correct": 238,
    "choices": [
      334,
      -391,
      141,
      238
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 x 20 =",
    "correct": 260,
    "choices": [
      260,
      52,
      345,
      -128
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 10 =",
    "correct": 100,
    "choices": [
      -48,
      -385,
      100,
      227
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 13 =",
    "correct": 247,
    "choices": [
      -55,
      -241,
      247,
      -47
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11 x 17 =",
    "correct": 187,
    "choices": [
      -81,
      187,
      141,
      281
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 10 =",
    "correct": 170,
    "choices": [
      170,
      -314,
      -332,
      -81
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 x 13 =",
    "correct": 169,
    "choices": [
      23,
      169,
      -150,
      261
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 x 14 =",
    "correct": 182,
    "choices": [
      -39,
      176,
      385,
      182
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 18 =",
    "correct": 216,
    "choices": [
      163,
      216,
      280,
      -147
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 14 =",
    "correct": 168,
    "choices": [
      -93,
      -180,
      168,
      -282
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 13 =",
    "correct": 208,
    "choices": [
      208,
      -53,
      12,
      61
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 15 =",
    "correct": 300,
    "choices": [
      300,
      118,
      -230,
      368
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 14 =",
    "correct": 238,
    "choices": [
      -69,
      341,
      183,
      238
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 11 =",
    "correct": 110,
    "choices": [
      -386,
      62,
      110,
      -290
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 17 =",
    "correct": 238,
    "choices": [
      -109,
      262,
      60,
      238
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 16 =",
    "correct": 224,
    "choices": [
      326,
      376,
      224,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 x 17 =",
    "correct": 306,
    "choices": [
      261,
      -193,
      -185,
      306
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11 x 12 =",
    "correct": 132,
    "choices": [
      132,
      270,
      -2,
      387
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 19 =",
    "correct": 304,
    "choices": [
      156,
      -373,
      304,
      92
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 12 =",
    "correct": 120,
    "choices": [
      120,
      -81,
      -178,
      -325
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 15 =",
    "correct": 240,
    "choices": [
      -148,
      73,
      -338,
      240
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 x 11 =",
    "correct": 143,
    "choices": [
      -135,
      143,
      -22,
      -166
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 x 18 =",
    "correct": 234,
    "choices": [
      -178,
      264,
      -349,
      234
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 15 =",
    "correct": 225,
    "choices": [
      -64,
      -252,
      335,
      225
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 20 =",
    "correct": 300,
    "choices": [
      296,
      300,
      -53,
      97
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 11 =",
    "correct": 209,
    "choices": [
      209,
      190,
      -396,
      72
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 x 19 =",
    "correct": 247,
    "choices": [
      -162,
      -111,
      247,
      -293
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 13 =",
    "correct": 130,
    "choices": [
      211,
      158,
      155,
      130
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 16 =",
    "correct": 304,
    "choices": [
      -391,
      304,
      -12,
      230
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 10 =",
    "correct": 140,
    "choices": [
      140,
      -157,
      -71,
      208
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 17 =",
    "correct": 238,
    "choices": [
      30,
      238,
      241,
      -274
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 15 =",
    "correct": 300,
    "choices": [
      -171,
      300,
      -117,
      -370
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 17 =",
    "correct": 255,
    "choices": [
      255,
      -269,
      -239,
      -26
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 15 =",
    "correct": 240,
    "choices": [
      -188,
      240,
      47,
      348
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 10 =",
    "correct": 160,
    "choices": [
      238,
      160,
      -279,
      305
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 14 =",
    "correct": 238,
    "choices": [
      238,
      155,
      135,
      -294
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 18 =",
    "correct": 252,
    "choices": [
      -301,
      -390,
      252,
      192
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 18 =",
    "correct": 270,
    "choices": [
      160,
      270,
      -319,
      145
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 x 12 =",
    "correct": 228,
    "choices": [
      38,
      228,
      -72,
      -175
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 14 =",
    "correct": 280,
    "choices": [
      280,
      -309,
      -178,
      -275
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 12 =",
    "correct": 192,
    "choices": [
      192,
      -257,
      -390,
      190
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 14 =",
    "correct": 280,
    "choices": [
      174,
      -240,
      164,
      280
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 13 =",
    "correct": 156,
    "choices": [
      239,
      156,
      -213,
      289
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 12 =",
    "correct": 240,
    "choices": [
      240,
      -216,
      304,
      -229
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 19 =",
    "correct": 228,
    "choices": [
      223,
      228,
      311,
      -13
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 13 =",
    "correct": 221,
    "choices": [
      360,
      334,
      43,
      221
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 x 11 =",
    "correct": 176,
    "choices": [
      176,
      199,
      258,
      -94
    ]
  }
]
